ILHAN YASSIN

ilham.hmyassin@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ilhamyassin (+673)8966344

A gradute of BSc in Computing from UTB that has experience with Entrepreneurship, Marketing, Creative Design, Photography and Videography. Enjoys brainstorming, learning and experiencing new skills and processes, while being flexible and quick to adapt to situations, especially in a fast paced and multi-task environment.

EXPERIENCE

Newgate Plus Co.

Business Development Officer

April 2015 - December 2016

Newgate Plus was a tech start-up and my responsibilities were in developing the business and pitching the business locally and internationally.

Mixbros Company

Marketing and Graphic Designer

August 2016 - April 2021

Mixbros is a F&B start-up dealing in creating craft mocktails. Responsibilities were in building the brand and marketing the products and the events attended.

Magic Media Studio

Graphic Design and Website Designer

December 2016 - July 2017

Attached here for University's work experience. Main responsibilities were graphic designing, creating pitch decks and designing the website for the company.

Photography and Graphic Designer

Freelance

June 2017 - February 2019

Freelanced as a photogrpaher mainly for events and products. Graphic design work mostly involved social media posts, logos and collaterals.

Bowlus / Shogun Media Co.

Design Lead and Photographer

February 2019 - February 2022

Creating brands, collaterals, guidelines, social media posts and promotional material for clients. I also had responsibilities as a Photographer and Videographer for Sports, Interviews, Events and Products.

EDUCATION

Universiti Teknologi Brunei

BSc (Hons) in Computing 2015-2018

Politeknik Brunei

Advanced Diploma in Information Systems and Technology 2012-2014

Pusat Tingkatan Enam Katok

GCE 'A' Level 2010-2011

TRAITS

- CreativeTeam Player
- Entrepreneurial
 Strategic Thinker
- ReliableOrganized
- Adaptable
 Diligent

SKILLS

- Adobe Illustrator
 Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Lightroom
 Adobe After Effects
- Adobe XD
 Public Speaking
- PhotographyVideography